quizmoz.com 2019-02-08

# QuizMoz

Your privacy is important to us. This privacy notice has been provided for you to understand how we use information and the choices that you can exercise for the collection and use of the information. Below, you can go through some of the important privacy practices adhered to by QUIZMOZ. 

**What type of user related information do we collect?**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the QUIZMOZ.com website. User related information is only collected on the registration page. The personal information collected is: 

Name 

Age

Sex

Address

Email address 

Information collection while recommending QUIZMOZ - When you recommend QUIZMOZ to anyone using the 'Suggest a Friend' page at www.QUIZMOZ.com/suggestmore.asp , the website collects the following information from you: 

Suggestor's name

Suggestor's email

Name and email of first friend

Name and email of second friend

Name and email of third friend

The Suggestor may furnish information on one, two or three friends. QUIZMOZ does not retain the suggestor's name or email, or any of the friends' names or email addresses on file for future use. Only a one time email from the suggestor is sent to the friend/s and the information gathered is not used for any other purpose.

QUIZMOZ also collects technical information related to your user session such as your IP address, browser type and operating system. This information is essential in giving you a personalized and user friendly interaction with the site. 

**How does QUIZMOZ use my information?**

The personal information collected by QUIZMOZ is only used to complete that order and no information is shared with outside parties. Personal information is not used for any marketing or commercial sale or exchange with third parties. We may use the information you supply us to contact you with matters related to your registration, purchase of exams, about your account status or to inform you about new QUIZMOZ offers. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

**Our commitment to data security**

Your personal information is kept strictly confidential through a well organized security system which only allows access to critical information to the company's security team members. This team consists of experienced engineers and staff who are under stringent confidentiality requirements. The security system is backed by the latest technology and ensures that your personal information is fully protected. Your QUIZMOZ profile which is available to you in your login area is protected through a password. You are advised to keep this password confidential and to ensure that you close the browser window after logging out from QUIZMOZ, especially if you are using a shared computer. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, while we do our utmost to protect your personal information, QUIZMOZ cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best efforts to ensure the security of your information on our systems. 

**Our commitment to payment information (credit card number) security**

QUIZMOZ services can be purchased online through a secure credit card transaction using any major credit card or PayPal. The ecommerce functionality on the site has been provided by WorldPay which is a trusted name in online transaction processing. When you supply your credit card information it is not retained on file by us. Moreover, the transaction takes place on the worldpay secure server which is 100% safe. When you buy any of our services, it is treated as a one time sale and your credit card will not be charged again in the future as is the case in subscription sales. PayPal transactions take place on the PayPal server which is a trusted name in online transaction processing. 

**How you can access or correct your personal information**

You can access and change the personal information that we collect and maintain by logging in at your user account with the username and passwords assigned to your account. The login page is at: 

The users Name cannot be directly changed by you from within the login so as to prevent unauthorized use of our testing services. You must request us for a change of Name by clicking on the "request name change" link within your login area. 

**What is our policy if there is a change in our Privacy practices?**

QUIZMOZ strives to improve the company's privacy policy from time to time. In such an eventuality, emails will automatically be sent out to all users describing the changes in the privacy policy and how they can opt out from the effects of the new privacy policy. Users will clearly be given an opportunity to prohibit any use of information that was not described at the time the initial user information was collected. Moreover, the link to the updated privacy policy will be clearly notified on the home page of the site. 

**What is QUIZMOZ's policy if the site is sold or merged with another company?**

QUIZMOZ will do its utmost to ensure that the successor adheres to the same privacy policy. However the privacy practices of the successor company cannot be ascertained before the eventuality of such a takeover occurs. QUIZMOZ will do its best to inform all registered users about the changes in the privacy practices as soon as the information about the new policy is made available. 

**Who should I contact if I have a Privacy related concern?**

If you have any doubts or require clarifications related to the privacy of your information with us, please use our contact form to get in touch with us.
